A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Departmental Reports, Series 28 FA370
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Reporting Format, 1963, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  Directives to state departments and agencies outling the procedures and format for filing quarterly reports, 1963-1966, and Agency Appraisal Reports, 1970
- Lists of Reports Received, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  Annual check list of quarterly reports received from state departments and agencies
- Forwarding Memos, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  Cover memos sent with quarterly reports from Dr. William J. Ronan, Secretary to the Governor, to Governor Rockefeller
- Forwarding Memos and Summaries, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  Cover memos and summaries of monthly reports from T. Norman Hurd, Secretary to the Governor, to Governor Rockefeller. Some include marginal notes by NAR.
- Forwarding Memos and Summaries, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 106)
- Forwarding Memos and Summaries, 1971-1973 (Box 5, Folder 107)